ps3maven.com 2015-09-05

# PS3Maven Privacy Policy | Ps3 Maven

## Privacy Policy

**PS3Maven Privacy Policy**

At [PS3Maven](http://ps3maven.com/), we respect your privacy and are committed to maintain policies which keep your privacy intact while browsing our website. The following information details our practices in regards to browsing the site, information gathering and more valid details as to our visits.

**Tracking**

We use regular analytics applications in order to track the visits to our site, which in turn includes the domain name, time, date and page visited. No personal information is provided during such a visit, but we study the details in order to improve our content…without sharing any such information with outside organizations for commercial use.

**Email**

We do not have your email address unless it was provided to us in one of the following ways:  
– Post comments: if you have commented on a post, an email address must be provided, yet it is not visible to the public nor is it shared with external sources. Such comments may also be displayed on a collaborating site (during Giveaway, Contests or Campaigns), yet no personal email identification will be present. Comments may also be removed if deemed offensive, abusive, interruptive, or for other requirements seemed necessary for the well being of the community and its members.  
– PS3Maven Newsletter: when subscribing to our Free Newsletter, you provide a valid email to receive the updates, yet this is also not shared with external organization or commercial use.

**Cookies**

Our collaborators and business partners may use cookies on our site such as advertisements, which maintain whether you have visited the site before or not. We do not have control over these cookies after permission to advertisers have been granted. However, no identifiable information is attached to such cookies.

**Advertisements**

We employ external Ad service companies for the display of advertisements on our site. Some of ads displayed may used cookies, but we do not have personal details or access to personal information.

Various advertisers we employ are Google Adsense, Technorati Media, etc. Since we display Google AdSense, we in fact must inform that Google AdSense uses DoubleClick Dart cookie, as to provide ‘ads tailored to your interests’. In order to provide additional details, we have added a direct link for further information regarding [DoubleClick Dart cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) and Google AdSense [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) and means to opt out od DoubleClick Dart cookie.

**External Links**

This Website includes links to external sites as well including product sales. PS3Maven is not responsible for external websites’ privacy policies, practices, content of such Websites or prices changes.

**Disclaimer**

PS3Maven provides content that is informational and opinion based content for Entertainment purposes only. While we may hope to provide the most updated and accurate information, PS3Maven makes no representation to accuracy, up-to-date, compatibility or validity of the content, and will not be liable or held accountable for errors, loss, injury or damage arising from its presence at PS3Maven. If inquiring further specific details, it is always recommended to find official documentation provided by company, product or brand interested in.

For further information or to reach us, we may be contacted at [contact@ps3maven.com](mailto:contact@xboxfreedom.com).

This policy may be updated at anytime, and may be found within the site. We encourage your feedback, opinions, and suggestions, these may be forwarded to contact@walyou.com

**Updated September 1, 2013**
